utsav acharya

sous chef

Profile

I am an experienced and passionate chef with 10+ years experiences in various restaurant and pub settings. I enjoy working in challenging environment and to be part of team to achieve a common goal. I like cooking good food and gives me great satisfaction to know that someone out there in enjoying my food.

Details

roxburgh park, Australia, 0416530591 utsav.acharya03@gmail.com

Skills

Ability to Multitask

Time Management

Leadership

Fast Learner

Communication Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Quality Assurance

Employment History

sous chef at Wesley Anne, Northcote

November 2018 — Present

Prepared good food, resulting in better dining experience. Worked effectively with all kitchen personnel, to promote happy working environment.

chef at Emerald Hotel, South Melbourne

September 2016 — August 2018

Make sure ready for service. Run kitchen while head chef is on day off. Making Ability to Work in a Team sure food is up to the standard.

chef at Ragusa Restaurant, Williamstown

September 2011 — August 2016

Helping to create the menu. Create homely Croatian and Mediterranean food. Food Safety and Sanitation Practices

cook at Dalmatino, Port Melbourne

September 2009 — August 2011

As a larder chef, making sure you are ready for service on your section. Learn as much as possible on the job. Do dishes and larder simultaneously during weekdays.

Education

Diploma of Hospitality Management, Australian Institute of Technology, Richmond

September 2008 — August 2010

Certificate III in comercial cookery, Australian Institute of Technology, Richmond

September 2008 — August 2010